KEYUR PATEL

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

**** +1 (408) 506 7277

✓ekeyur@gmail.com • ekeyur.com

nttps://github.com/ekeyur

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ekeyur

PROFILE

I have over 5 years of management consulting, 2 years of product management experience and I have been developing full Stack projects for over 6 months. I am currently seeking opportunities where I can put my skills to good use and improve my problemsolving abilities. I have a love for learning new skills, and enjoy working on teams.

EDUCATION

DigitalCrafts

SEPT 2016 - JAN 2017 Certificate Full Stack Development

Georgia Institute of Technology

AUG 2003 - JULY 2007 Bachelor of Science Industrial Engineering (Optimization)

SKILLS

NODE.JS

ANGULARJS POSTGRESQL ANGULAR 4 MONGODB **JAVASCRIPT GITHUB JOUERY** AMAZON AWS

EXPRESS MEAN PYTHON VUEJS

BOOTSTRAP FLASK

HOBBIES

Reading | Running | Biking | Ping Pong

TDD (JASMINE)

EXPERIENCE

Digital Crafts, Developer in Residence / Student

SEPT 2016 - APRIL 2017

Developer in Residence [FEB 2017 - APRIL 2017]

- Assisted students' in debugging their code on different assignments
- Mentored the new students on programming techniques
- Assisted the instructor in creating new material and quiz
- Filled in for instructor and continued the curriculum

AirNavAtl: An app to navigate inside of Atlanta airport

- Created using Python, AngularJS, PostGreSQL & Leaflet API
- Used Dijkstra's algorithm to find the shortest path
- Mainly contributed in backend and api generation
- Demo available at: https://airnavatl.com

TripGoalie: An app to facilitate safe travel on MARTA

- Participated in a 24 hour MARTA hosted hackathon for nonprofits
- Developed using Python, Flask, Jinja 2 and PostGreSQL
- Demo available at: http://tripgoalie.com

Fabulari: Speech modeling app for kids with disabilities

- Developed using AngularJS, MongoDB, Express and Node.js
- Contributed to database schema design and backend APIs and helped build AngularJS logic on the front end
- Demo available at: http://fabulari.org

Grillber: A rental service for Big Green Eggs

- Developed using Python, Flask, Jinja 2 and PostGreSQL
- Contributed to database schema design, backend logic and implemented stripe
- Demo available at: http://grillber.com

Realization, Product Manager / Strategy Consultant

SEPT 2008 - SEPT 2016

Product Manager, Concerto (2014 - 2016)

- Responsible for coming up with new features to be developed
- Created user stories and prioritized development queues
- Interfaced with UI/UX designers for wireframes and design approval
- Interfaced with stakeholders to gather requirements and the direction of the product
- Created user stories for developers and snippets on product updates for marketing
- Created product demos for use in the field for sales team

Management Strategy Consultant (2008 - 2014)

- Developed and implemented strategies and processes to improve project deliveries in multiple industries
- Trained consultants on data gathering, data analysis and client investigations on site
- Accompanied sales directors to answer any technical questions on the product